[upbeat rock music]
[欢快的摇滚音乐]
- [sighs]
[whistling]
[吹口哨]
So, what you guys doing?
那么，你们在做什么？
Playing chess?
在下棋吗？
- What are you doing? Stating the obvious?
你在做什么？陈述显而易见的事实？
- Sorry. I'm just bored.
对不起。我只是无聊。
Mae is so late--she was supposed to be here, like...
梅太晚了——她应该在这里，比如...
three minutes ago.
三分钟前。
- Well, we need quiet.
嗯，我们需要安静。
Yeah, right, quiet. [mutters]
是啊，对，安静。[低声嘀咕]
[whispers] You know I don't do well when Mae's not around.
[低语]你知道梅不在的时候我表现不好。
- Shh. I need to concentrate.
- 嘘。我需要集中注意力。
I've never beaten Ricky before.
我以前从没赢过里基。
- Ooh, looks like that's about to change.
- 哦，看来这就要改变了。
- Really? - Shh.
- 真的吗？ - 嘘。
Your move.
该你走了。
- Ooh.
- 哦。
[mutters]
[低声嘀咕]
Eeh.
哎。
Zzz.... - Dawn, you can't help him!
Zzz.... - 晨曦，你不能帮他！
- My bad. It's just that this game could take all "knight,"
- 我的错。只是这个游戏可能会耗尽所有“骑士”的时间，
even though Nicky's up-"pawn" victory.
尽管尼基已经接近“兵”的胜利。
- Knight takes pawn. Boom!
- 骑士吃兵。砰！
- Checkmate. - Wha--
- 将军。 - 什--
Seriously?
真的吗？
I thought you were helping me. - I thought I was too.
我以为你在帮我。 - 我也以为我在帮你。
Well, at least for a moment, you had hope.
好吧，至少有那么一刻，你还有希望。
- Which is worse than losing on my own.
- 这比我自己输掉还要糟糕。
You know, I didn't think losing could be anymore painful,
你知道吗，我没想到输掉会这么痛苦，
but you know what, you did it.
但你知道吗，你做到了。
- And normally, I enjoy beating Nicky,
我通常喜欢打败尼基，
but you made it so easy, that you took all the joy out of it.
但你让它变得太容易了，以至于你剥夺了所有的乐趣。
- Well, at least you guys are talking to me.
至少你们现在愿意和我说话了。
I was kind of bored.
我有点无聊。
- You always do this, Dawn.
你总是这样，Dawn。
Whenever Mae's not around, you ruin whatever we're doing.
每当Mae不在的时候，你就毁了我们正在做的事情。
- Let's go again.
我们再来一次。
- [sighs]
叹气
- Sorry I'm late, Dawn, but I have huge news.
对不起我迟到了，Dawn，但我有个大消息。
I just got accepted to Hawk Crest Academy!
我刚刚被Hawk Crest Academy录取了！
- The boarding school that wait-listed you?
- 那个把你列入候补名单的寄宿学校？
- Now they're the boarding school that un-wait-listed me!
- 现在他们是我被移出候补名单的寄宿学校了！
[both shriek]
[两人尖叫]
- I'm so happy for you!
- 我真为你高兴！
When do you start, next year? - Next week.
你什么时候开始，明年吗？ - 下周。
- You mean next week of next year?
- 你是说下周的明年？
- No, next week of next week!
- 不，下周的下周！
both: Uh-oh.
两人: 哎呀。
- Why aren't you jumping anymore?
- 你怎么不跳了？
- You really start next week?
你真的下周就开始吗？
- Yeah.
嗯。
Somebody dropped out, and I got their spot.
有人退出了，我顶替了他们的位置。
How lucky is that? - So lucky.
多幸运啊？ - 非常幸运。
[chuckles] Wow, my BFF gets to get into her dream school.
哇，我的闺蜜要进入她的梦想学校了。
Did you hear that, guys? - We heard.
你们听到了吗？ - 听到了。
- Mazel tov.
恭喜。
- To her dream school,
向她的梦想学校，
which is in a different city... [chuckles]
在一个不同的城市... [轻笑]
Far, far away.
很远，很远的地方。
You know I don't do well when Mae's not around.
你知道当Mae不在的时候，我表现不好。
- Neither do we.
- 我们也是。
- Yeah, I think we both just got check-"Mae'd."
- 是啊，我想我们俩都被'Mae效应'影响了。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
[whistling]
[口哨声]
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ 嘿！ ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
[cheerful music]
[欢快的音乐]
- Wow, so you're really going away to boarding school next week?
哇，所以你真的下周就要去寄宿学校了？
That's just wow!
真是太惊讶了！
- Speaking of wow,
说到惊讶，
that's the school observatory,
那是学校的观星台，
and that's the equestrian center.
还有那个是马术中心。
I can learn dressage.
我可以学习盛装舞步。
I don't even know what that is, but I can learn it.
我甚至不知道那是什么，但我可以学。
- It's choreographed horse dancing.
就是编排好的马术舞蹈。
See, now you don't have to go away to that school.
看，现在你不用去那所学校了。
- [laughs] You're hilarious, Dawn.
（笑）你真有趣，Dawn。
It's gonna be so much fun when you visit on the weekends.
你周末来访一定会很有趣的。
Plus, we can FaceShack and SnapBlab.
而且，我们可以用FaceShack和SnapBlab。
- Yeah, you know what, when you really think about it,
- 是啊，你知道吗，当你真正思考时，
nothing's gonna change.
什么都不会改变。
- Everything's gonna change. Look how crazy Dawn got
- 一切都会改变。看看Dawn在Mae不在的三分钟里变得多么疯狂。
when Mae wasn't here for three minutes.
Mae一去不复返，我们的计划就泡汤了。
With Mae gone for good, our goose is cooked.
- 也许我们的计划没问题。
- Maybe our goose is fine.
也许我们低估了Dawn。
Maybe we're underestimating Dawn.
也许她会比我们想象的处理得更好。
Maybe she'll handle it better than we think.
- 老实说，能进入Hawk Crest对我来说是梦想成真。
- Honestly, getting into Hawk Crest
老实说，能进入鹰冠庄园
is a dream come true for me.
对我来说简直是梦想成真。
- Well, if it's a dream come true for you,
嗯，如果对你来说是梦想成真，
it's a dream come true for me.
那对我也是。
- See? Our goose is good.
看吧？我们的情况还不错。
Dawn's taking it in stride.
Dawn处理得很好。
- Or maybe she's faking it.
或者她可能在假装。
- I don't think so.
我不这么认为。
Whenever Dawn fakes being okay with something,
每当Dawn假装对某事没意见时，
her voice gets all high-pitched.
她的声音会变得很高。
[computer trills]
- Ooh, it's Amber, my soon-to-be roommate.
哦，是安柏，我即将成为室友的人。
- [high-pitched] Did you say "roommate"?
你说‘室友’？
- [high-pitched] Did she just say "roommate"?
她刚才是说‘室友’吗？
- Hi, Amber. - Hi, Mae.
嗨，安柏。
I can't wait for you to get to school.
我迫不及待等你来学校。
I saw our new room today, and it has bunk beds!
我今天看了我们的新房间，有双层床！
- Bunk beds? - [high-pitched] Bunk beds?
双层床？
- Goose cooking! - We're fine,
until she drifts into the high-pitched gibberish.
她开始说些高音的胡言乱语之前，我们都还好。
- Isn't Amber great?
- Amber不是很好吗？
- [pitch heightening] Yeah, she seems really sweet...
- [音调升高] 是啊，她看起来真的很甜美...
[high-pitched gibberish]
[高音胡言乱语]
- We need to find Dawn a new Mae!
- 我们需要给Dawn找个新的Mae！
[mug shatters] - [high-pitched gibberish]
[杯子碎裂声] - [高音胡言乱语]
- And you a new "I Heart Sweater Vests" mug.
- 还有给你一个新的“我爱毛衣背心”杯子。
And a new sweater vest.
还有一件新的毛衣背心。
♪ ♪
- Thank you for coming to the rose ceremony,
- 感谢你来参加玫瑰仪式，
where we will be determining
我们将在这里决定
which one of you will become Dawn's new best friend.
你们中的哪一位将成为Dawn的新闺蜜。
- Rose ceremony? I thought you said
- 玫瑰仪式？我以为你说是
we were just coming here for free sandwiches.
我们只是来这里吃免费三明治的。
- Yeah, and I've already got best friends.
- 是的，而且我已经有了最好的朋友。
both: Who?
两人: 谁？
- You guys.
- 你们。
- Oh, yeah, right.
- 哦，对，没错。
- Forget this--I'm taking my free sandwich and leaving.
- 算了——我要拿我的免费三明治然后离开。
- There are no sandwiches.
- 这里没有三明治。
- No sandwiches? - Mm-mm.
- 没有三明治？ - 嗯嗯。
- Then I'm taking the rose and leaving.
那我就拿这朵玫瑰走人。
- Then we can't have a rose ceremony!
那我们就不能举行玫瑰仪式了！
- No "ceremonay"? Then I'm taking the "doilay."
没有‘仪式’？那我就拿这个‘装饰纸’。
- Oh.
哦。
- No sandwiches, no doily,
没有三明治，没有装饰纸，
no best friends?
没有最好的朋友？
I'm taking the tray.
我拿这个托盘。
- Well, that went south fast.
哎，这事儿一下子就搞砸了。
- Tell me about it. That was Grandma's good tray!
说得太对了。那可是奶奶的好托盘！
- No, we need to expand our search
不，我们需要扩大搜索范围
to find Dawn a new best friend.
为了给Dawn找到一个新的好朋友。
- Well, looks like I'll just have to turn on
- 好吧，看来我得开启
the ol' Ricky charm.
老Ricky的魅力了。
[clicks tongue]
[咂舌]
- This should be fun.
- 这应该会很有趣。
Mm. [mumbles]
嗯。[咕哝]
And here comes the dry lips...
现在轮到干燥的嘴唇了...
- [lips smacking]
- [咂嘴]
- And now the sweaty palm...
- 还有出汗的手掌...
- Hi.
- 嗨。
[grunts]
[咕哝声]
- And now the girl leaves.
- 现在女孩离开了。
- [mumbles]
- [含糊不清]
[sighs]
[叹气]
- Hey, how'd that go? - [high-pitched] Great!
- 嘿，怎么样了？ - [高音] 很好！
- Really? 'Cause it was like watching a bad movie
- 真的吗？因为那就像在看一部糟糕透顶的电影
with a terrible, terrible cast.
有着糟糕至极的演员阵容。
- Cast. That's it.
- 演员阵容。就是它了。
That's how we'll solve our Dawn problem.
这就是我们解决Dawn问题的方法。
- Genius--we find a girl with a broken leg,
- 天才——我们找一个腿受伤的女孩，
two legs if we're lucky, we place her in front of Dawn,
如果我们幸运的话，两条腿都断了，我们把她放在Dawn面前，
Dawn signs her cast, boom! BFFs.
Dawn在她的石膏上签名，砰！成了最好的朋友。
- Or... we say we're making a movie,
- 或者...我们说我们在拍一部电影，
and audition girls to be cast as Dawn's best friend.
然后试镜女孩们，让她们扮演Dawn最好的朋友。
- Well, that sounds like a lot more work, but okay.
- 嗯，那听起来工作量大多了，但好吧。
[upbeat rock music]
[欢快的摇滚音乐]
- Tom, I'm worried about Dawn.
- Tom，我担心Dawn。
- Well, she seems okay.
- 嗯，她看起来还好。
Her voice isn't doing that high-pitched thing anymore.
她的声音不再那么尖锐了。
- ♪ She's Mae and I'm Dawn ♪
- ♪ 她是Mae，我是Dawn ♪
[plays blues riff]
[演奏蓝调即兴片段]
♪ I miss her bad and she ain't even gone ♪
♪ 我非常想念她，尽管她还没离开 ♪
♪ ♪
♪ We had good times I'll always remember ♪
♪ 我们曾有过美好时光，我将永远铭记 ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Now she'll be having them with her roomie... ♪
♪ 现在她将与室友一起度过那些时光... ♪
"Amber."
“安柏。”
♪ ♪
- Got the blues, huh?
- 心情低落了，是吧？
- I got 'em bad, Daddy-o. [continues playing]
- 我真的很糟糕，老爹。[继续演奏]
- Okay, you wanna talk about it,
- 好吧，你想谈谈这件事，
rather than keep singing?
- 而不是继续唱歌吗？
- Not now, Mamma Jamma.
- 现在不行，妈妈大人。
- Okay, we're gonna take five.
- 好的，我们休息五分钟。
Here. - Oh, wow.
给你。- 哇哦。
Look, everybody has a roommate at boarding school.
听着，寄宿学校里每个人都有室友。
It's no big deal. [grunts]
没什么大不了的。
- It's a very big deal. It's a huge deal.
- 这是个大问题。这是个巨大的问题。
Now "Amber" gets to be closer to Mae than I am.
现在“琥珀”可以比我还亲近梅了。
- Honey, you and Mae will always be close.
- 亲爱的，你和梅永远都会很亲密。
- Not in distance, but--
- 不是在距离上，而是——
Mamma Jorker!
乔克妈妈！
- I'm gonna miss out on a ton of new experiences with Mae.
- 我会错过和梅一起的许多新体验。
Every first Mae has from now on
从现在开始，梅的每一个第一次
will be with "Amber," not me.
都会是和“安伯”一起，而不是我。
"Amber" gets to be Mae's first roommate,
“安伯”将成为梅的第一个室友，
and I wanted to be Mae's first roommate.
而我本想成为梅的第一个室友。
"Amber"...
“安伯”……
- What's more important, being Mae's first roommate
- 更重要的是，成为梅的第一个室友
or being Mae's first best friend?
还是成为梅的第一个最好的朋友？
- Why can't I be both?
- 为什么我不能两者都是？
- Honey, Mae already has a roommate.
- 亲爱的，Mae已经有室友了。
- Sorry, sweetie, I know it's hard to accept,
- 对不起，宝贝，我知道这很难接受，
but sometimes, we can't have everything.
- 但有时候，我们不能拥有一切。
Aw. [smooches]
哎。[亲吻]
- We love you, kiddo. [smooches]
- 我们爱你，孩子。[亲吻]
- Hold on.
- 等等。
Maybe I can have everything.
也许我可以拥有一切。
[upbeat rock music]
[欢快的摇滚音乐]
♪ ♪
[knocks on door]
[敲门声]
[playing "When the Saints Go Marching In"]
[演奏《当圣徒进军时》]
♪ Oh, when the Dawn ♪
♪ 哦，当黎明 ♪
♪ Comes moving in ♪
♪ 来临 ♪
♪ Oh, when the Dawn comes moving in ♪
♪ 哦，当黎明来临 ♪
Hey, roomie, surprise!
嘿，室友，惊喜！
♪ ♪
[upbeat rock music]
[欢快的摇滚音乐]
- Wow, there is a lot of room in these drawers.
- 哇，这些抽屉里空间真大。
- That's because I've been emptying them.
- 那是因为我一直在清空它们。
- [whistling] - Because I've been packing?
- [吹口哨] - 因为我一直在打包？
Because I'm leaving for school in a few days?
因为我几天后就要去学校了？
- I know, and we're gonna be roommates until you go.
- 我知道，在我们走之前我们会一直是室友。
This way, we're not only first best friends,
这样，我们不仅是第一个最好的朋友，
we're also first roommates.
也是第一个室友。
- Dawn, I really don't have time for this.
- 黎明，我真的没有时间做这个。
- You're right, we need to speed things up.
- 你说得对，我们需要加快速度。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
There, all moved in.
好了，搬进来了。
Now we have time for our first roommate pizza party.
现在我们有时间举办我们的第一次室友披萨派对。
What kinda pizza do you want? - I don't--
你想要什么口味的披萨？ - 我不——
- Yeah, you know what, I'm gonna surprise you.
- 是的，你知道吗，我要给你一个惊喜。
Hi, I'd like to order one First Roommate Surprise.
你好，我想订一个‘第一次室友惊喜’披萨。
Yeah, it's half first roommate,
是的，一半是第一次室友，
half first best friend. [chuckles]
一半是第一次最好的朋友。[轻笑]
[whispers] It's a meat lovers.
[低语] 是肉食爱好者的。
♪ ♪
- All right, time to get the audition started.
- 好了，是时候开始试镜了。
- I still don't understand why you get to be the director.
我还是不明白为什么你是导演。
- Because I'm wearing the hat and the scarf.
因为我戴着帽子和围巾。
- It's not even your scarf. It's Dawn's.
那甚至不是你的围巾，是Dawn的。
- Oh, so you think you can pull off wearing Dawn's scarf?
哦，所以你觉得自己能戴上Dawn的围巾？
- Well, I'm pulling off wearing her deodorant.
好吧，我正在用她的除臭剂。
- That's not something you say to win an argument.
这不是赢得争论时该说的话。
All right, who's our first audition?
好吧，我们的第一个试镜者是谁？
- Ethel.
Ethel。
- Ethel? Yeah, I don't think so.
Ethel？不，我不这么认为。
Who's after Ethel?
Ethel之后是谁？
- Thank you for coming.
谢谢你的到来。
Please, have a seat.
请坐。
- You'll be reading the part of Dawn's new BFF,
你将扮演Dawn的新闺蜜，
and Ricky will be reading the part of Dawn.
而Ricky将扮演Dawn。
- Why are you handing me this?
你为什么给我这个？
- It's the Dawn wig.
这是Dawn的假发。
Put it on.
戴上它。
- You put it on.
你戴上吧。
You're already wearing Dawn's scarf.
你已经戴着Dawn的围巾了。
- Well, yeah, but you're wearing her deodorant.
嗯，是的，但你用了她的除臭剂。
And not enough of it.
而且还不够多。
- Great, she's gone.
太好了，她走了。
- Diva. - [scoffs] I know, right?
真是个戏精。
- I was talking about you.
我知道，对吧？
Ready, Marcia? And action.
我是在说你。
- Mae, it's me, Dawn. What's on your mind?
准备好了吗，玛西亚？开始。
- I gotta ask, are we best friends?
梅，是我，Dawn。你在想什么？
Are we not best friends?
我得问一下，我们是最好的朋友吗？
Mama...
我们不是最好的朋友吗？
has to know.
妈妈...必须知道。
[both sigh] - Marcia, Marcia, Marcia.
[两人叹气] - 玛西亚，玛西亚，玛西亚。
- Thanks for coming in.
- 谢谢你过来。
- I'm sorry, I didn't have time to prepare.
- 对不起，我没时间准备。
I dropped the script in my pool.
我把剧本掉进游泳池里了。
both: Pool?
两人: 游泳池？
- It took my butler forever to dry it.
- 我的管家花了好长时间才把它弄干。
both: Butler?
两人: 管家？
- Will you excuse us for a second?
- 你能让我们单独待一会儿吗？
We're going about this the wrong way.
我们这样做是错的。
Mae is nice, sweet, caring,
梅很好，甜美，关心人，
the best friend Dawn could ever ask for.
Dawn能拥有的最好的朋友。
But have we ever benefited from their friendship?
但我们从她们的友谊中得到过什么好处吗？
- No. Never!
- 没有。从来没有！
- Exactly.
- 没错。
So, why don't we find a new best friend for Dawn,
那么，我们为什么不帮Dawn找一个新的最好的朋友，
from whom we can also reap some benefits?
同时我们也能从中获得一些好处呢？
- Like a pool
- 比如一个游泳池
and a butler!
和一个管家！
- Why stop there?
- 为什么要就此打住？
I'm sure one of these girls has even more to offer.
我相信这些女孩中肯定有人能提供更多。
Hey, Marcia, can you hang out for a little while?
嘿，玛西娅，你能稍微待一会儿吗？
We have some more girls to see.
我们还有一些女孩要见。
- Who's next?
- 下一个是谁？
- Bertha. - Bertha?
- 伯莎。 - 伯莎？
Ethel! You're back in.
埃塞尔！你回来了。
♪ ♪
- Wow, we ate that whole pizza.
- 哇，我们把整个披萨都吃完了。
What an experience that will never be topped
那真是一次无法被超越的经历
by any other experience with anyone ever!
是任何其他人无法带来的体验！
So, what do you wanna do next?
那么，你接下来想做什么？
- I should really get back to packing.
- 我真的应该回去打包了。
- Perfect, you pack,
- 好极了，你打包，
and I'll take care of the bunk beds.
- 我来负责上下铺。
- Bunk beds?
- 上下铺？
- Uh, yeah, they're essential to
- 呃，是的，上下铺是
the whole first roommate, best friend experience.
- 整个初次室友、最佳朋友体验的关键。
Ooh...
- 哦...
Hi, yeah, I'd like for you to put aside
- 你好，是的，我希望你能预留
one roommate surprise bunk bed.
- 一张室友惊喜的上下铺。
Yeah. Yeah, it's half first roommate,
- 是的。是的，它一半是初次室友，
half first best friend.
一半是第一个最好的朋友。
[chuckles]
[轻笑]
[whispers] It's the cheapest bunk bed you have.
[低语] 这是你们最便宜的上下铺。
♪ ♪
- Congratulations, ladies, you are the two final actresses
- 恭喜，女士们，你们是最后两位争夺Dawn新BFF角色的女演员。
up for the role of Dawn's new BFF.
- 这对我们来说是个艰难的决定。
- This is a tough decision for us.
你们俩都有自己的优势。
You both have your strengths.
Marcia，你的无畏、努力、管家和加热泳池真的让你脱颖而出。
Marcia, your fearlessness, effort,
- 而Danielle，镜头喜欢你...
butler, and heated pool have really set you apart.
- [咯咯笑] - 还有你父母的游艇
- And Danielle, the camera loves you...
- 而丹妮尔，镜头特别喜欢你...
- [giggles] - And your parents' yacht
- [咯咯笑] - 还有你父母的游艇
and private jet.
- 和私人飞机。
- Right now, it's too close to call.
- 现在，胜负难分。
Do either of you have anything else
- 你们俩还有没有其他什么
you can bring to the role? - Say, a trampoline, jet skis?
- 可以为这个角色带来的？比如说，蹦床，水上摩托？
- Motorcycle with a sidecar we can both ride in?
- 带边车的摩托车，我们可以一起骑？
- What does any of this have to do with acting?
- 这些和演戏有什么关系？
- You're out, Marcia!
- 你出局了，玛西亚！
We don't have time for difficult actresses!
- 我们没时间应付难搞的女演员！
- What? - Hit the bricks, sister!
- 什么？ - 走开，姐姐！
Congrats, Danielle, you're our new private jet.
恭喜，Danielle，你是我们的新私人飞机。
- BFF. - BFF.
- 最好的朋友。 - 最好的朋友。
♪ ♪
- So, I'll put up pictures of my cat, Debbie.
- 那么，我会贴上我猫的照片，Debbie。
- No way.
- 不可能。
And I can put up pictures of my cat, Debbie.
我也会贴上我猫的照片，Debbie。
both: Double Debbies!
双方：双Debbies！
[screwdriver whirring]
[螺丝刀旋转声]
What is that noise?
那是什么声音？
- Don't mind me!
别管我！
Yeah, it turns out even the cheapest bunk beds
是啊，即使是最低价的双层床
are kinda pricy,
也有点贵
so I got some wood out of the dumpster at Get Sporty,
所以我从Get Sporty的垃圾箱里弄了些木头
and I figured I'd DIY it... [screwdriver whirs]
打算自己动手做...
Dawn It Yourself.
黎明自己来。
- Who is that? - Oh, sorry.
那是谁？
Amber, meet Dawn, Dawn, Amber.
哦，抱歉
- Hi, nice to-- [whirring]
Amber，这是Dawn，Dawn，这是Amber。
- Oh, sorry,
嗨，很高兴—
looks like I just had one more righty to tighty.
看起来我刚完成了一个右紧的活儿。
You were saying?
你刚才说什么？
- I was just saying it's so nice to--
我刚才说，很高兴——
[whirring]
（嗡嗡声）
- Nice to meet you, Hamper.
很高兴见到你，Hamper。
- Anyway, we have a big decision to make.
总之，我们有一个重要的决定要做。
There's a tradition at Hawk Crest,
在Hawk Crest有一个传统，
where new roommates choose a unique experience
新室友会选择一个独特的经历
that only they will share.
只有他们俩会分享。
It bonds them forever.
这会让他们永远紧密相连。
- Forever?
永远？
- Oh, cool. What did you have in mind?
哦，酷。你有什么想法？
I'm down for whatever you wanna do.
我随你，你想做什么都行。
- Great, 'cause I wanna do something
太好了，因为我想要做一件
everyone at school will be talking about:
学校里每个人都会谈论的事情：
Skydiving! - [scoffs] Skydiving?
跳伞！
Please. Mae's afraid of heights.
跳伞？
- I love it, and it'll definitely be a first.
拜托，梅怕高。
- Uh, we should probably do our first
我喜欢，这绝对会是个第一次。
before that first, though.
呃，我们应该在那之前先做我们的第一次。
We gotta go, Hamhock.
我们得走了，Hamhock。
It's time for bunk bed bonding night.
是时候进行上下铺联谊夜了。
Ooh! I call top.
哦！我要睡上铺。
[creaking]
[吱吱作响]
[clatters, crashes]
[咔嚓声，碰撞声]
Hey, look at that.
嘿，看那个。
I can skydive too.
我也能跳伞。
[squealing softly] - [sighs]
[轻轻尖叫] - [叹气]
- ♪ Mae kicked me out ♪
- ♪ Mae把我踢出来了 ♪
♪ I'm feeling so gloomy ♪
♪ 我感到如此忧郁 ♪
♪ As it turns out ♪
♪ 事实证明 ♪
♪ I won't be her first roomy... ♪
♪ 我不会成为她的第一个室友... ♪
[voice modulating] [plays blues riff]
[声音调节] [演奏蓝调 riff]
[cheerful music]
[欢快音乐]
- Okay, there's no script this time.
- 好吧，这次没有剧本。
We need to improvise a scene
我们需要即兴创作一个场景
with the actress who's playing Dawn.
和扮演 Dawn 的女演员一起。
That's her.
就是她。
- Well, I guess your Dawn's best friend now.
- 嗯，我想你现在成了 Dawn 最好的朋友了。
Are these your manis or your pedis?
这些是你的美甲还是足疗？
- Hey, Dawn, sorry to...
嘿，Dawn，抱歉打扰...
interrupt, but we wanted you to meet someone.
我们想让你见个人。
- And action.
开始。
- Hi, I'm Danielle. - Oh, hi, I'm Dawn.
嗨，我是Danielle。
Sorry, I'm really not in the mood to meet anyone right now.
哦，嗨，我是Dawn。
- Oh, you poor thing.
抱歉，我现在真的没心情见任何人。
Shh, everything's gonna be okay.
哦，你这可怜的家伙。
No, that didn't feel right.
嘘，一切都会好起来的。
Let me try again.
不，那样感觉不对。
Maybe I should have an accent.
让我再试一次。也许我应该带点口音。
- I can't believe you guys.
- 真不敢相信你们。
- It's not what you think. - Yeah.
- 不是你想的那样。 - 是的。
- So, it's not that you were afraid I'd ruin your lives
- 所以，并不是因为你们担心我会毁了你们的生活
without Mae in town, so you faked producing a movie
没有梅在镇上，所以你们假装要制作一部电影
and auditioned girls to play the part of my new best friend?
并试镜女孩来扮演我的新闺蜜？
- Okay, it's exactly what you think.
- 好吧，正是你想的那样。
- This may be your worst plan ever.
- 这可能是你们最糟糕的计划了。
- Please, her parents own a private jet.
- 拜托，她父母拥有一架私人飞机。
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. Private jet?
- 哇，哇，哇。私人飞机？
Can we skydive out of it? - I guess.
我们可以从上面跳伞吗？ - 我想可以。
- [British accent] 'Ello, 'ello, I'm Danielle,
- [英式口音] 你好，你好，我是Danielle，
and everything's going to be jolly good!
一切都会非常顺利的！
- Yes. Yes, it is, Private Jet.
- 是的，是的，私人飞机。
- Danielle. - Danielle.
- Danielle。 - Danielle。
[upbeat rock music]
[欢快的摇滚音乐]
♪ ♪
- I'm super psyched we're doing this, Mae!
- 我超级兴奋我们正在做这件事，Mae！
Can you believe we're gonna jump out of a plane?
你能相信我们要从飞机上跳下去吗？
- No, I cannot! - I mean, are we crazy or what?
- 不，我不能！ - 我是说，我们是不是疯了？
- I'm definitely going with crazy!
- 我绝对同意是疯了！
- Okay, we're approaching the drop zone!
好的，我们正在接近跳伞区！
The instructor's in the cockpit,
教练在驾驶舱里，
so I'm just gonna go over some last-minute
所以我只是要给他过一遍最后的
safety instructions for him.
安全指示。
Oops.
哎呀。
I mean, that's good luck!
我是说，那是好运气！
Make a wish!
许个愿吧！
- Oh, hey, Mae, Miles, Hamburger.
哦，嘿，Mae，Miles，Hamburger。
So, today's the big bond day, huh?
所以，今天是重要的联结日，对吧？
- What are you doing here?
你在这里做什么？
- And where did you come from?
- 你是从哪儿来的？
- The important thing is, I got here before Mae jumped!
- 重要的是，我比Mae先跳下来！
Oh. [grunts]
哦。
And I found this!
我找到了这个！
- Yeah, that's mine.
- 对，那是我的。
See? This is what I was for.
看吧？这就是我来的目的。
- So, any other surprises I should know about?
- 那么，还有其他我应该知道的惊喜吗？
- Surprises? Psh, no!
- 惊喜？没有！
But we should probably move away from the door!
但我们可能应该远离门口！
- Why?
- 为什么？
- Hey, everybody!
嘿，大家好！
- Seriously, where are you guys coming from?
说真的，你们从哪儿来的？
- Is he okay?
他没事吧？
- Probably.
大概没事。
We should probably move away from the door.
我们可能应该离开门口。
- Why?
为什么？
- [British accent] 'Ello, 'ello, I'm Danielle,
你好，你好，我是Danielle，
Dawn's new best friend.
Dawn的新闺蜜。
- New best-- are you replacing me?
新闺蜜——你要取代我吗？
- If anybody's replacing anybody,
如果有人要取代谁，
it's you replacing me.
是你在取代我。
It should've been me and you
本来应该是我和你一起从飞机上跳下来。
jumping out of a plane together.
道恩，你和我永远不会一起做这件事。
- Dawn, you and I would've never done this together.
为什么不呢？
- Why not? - Because I'm scared to death!
因为我怕得要死！
- Then why are you jumping with Hammertoe?
那为什么要和汉默托一起跳呢？
- Because I wanted Hammertoe to like me...
因为我想让汉默托喜欢我...
And skydiving actually seemed less scary than leaving you,
而且跳伞实际上比离开你更不恐怖,
my first best friend.
我的第一个最好的朋友。
- Aww.
哎呀。
- Dawn, you and I will always be firsties, forever.
- 黎明，你和我永远是最好的朋友，永远。
And I'm sorry.
而且我很抱歉。
I was so stressed out about leaving,
我离开的压力太大了，
I didn't consider how hard this would be for you.
我没有考虑到这对你来说有多难。
- [stammers] No, I'm sorry.
- [结巴] 不，对不起。
A real firstie would never stop her bestie
一个真正的朋友永远不会阻止她的好朋友
from taking advantage of such a great opportunity.
抓住这样一个绝佳的机会。
I really am happy for you.
我真的为你感到高兴。
- Aww.
- 哎呀。
- All the hugs are really sweet,
- 所有的拥抱真的很甜蜜，
but someone has to tell me,
但总得有人告诉我，
where did you guys come from?
你们是从哪儿冒出来的？
- Danielle's dad has a plane,
- 丹妮尔的爸爸有一架飞机，
a nice one, right, Ricky?
一架不错的，对吧，里基？
- I just wanna say,
- 我只想说，
I can't wait to do this movie with you guys.
我迫不及待想和你们一起拍这部电影。
- Movie? - What movie?
- 电影？ - 什么电影？
- Yeah, since Dawn's gonna be okay,
- 是的，既然道恩会没事，
we no longer need the role of new best friend.
我们不再需要新闺蜜的角色了。
- I'm out of the movie?
- 我被踢出电影了？
- Sorry, that's show biz, kid.
- 抱歉，这就是演艺圈，孩子。
- That's okay, I'm rich!
- 没关系，我很有钱！
- What--we can still use your parents' private jet, right?
- 什么——我们还是可以借用你父母的私人飞机，对吧？
- No!
- 不行！
- We're about to leave the drop zone.
- 我们即将离开跳伞区。
Do you still wanna jump with me?
你还想和我一起跳吗？
- Sorry, but if I were to ever jump out of a plane,
- 抱歉，但如果我真要从飞机上跳下来，
it would be with Dawn. - I get it.
那一定是要和Dawn一起。 - 我明白。
We'll figure out another bonding moment.
我们会找到其他增进感情的时刻。
See you at school!
学校见！
- So, since we're up here, I gotta ask:
- 既然我们都上来了，我得问一下：
Are we jumping out of this plane?
我们要从这架飞机上跳下去吗？
Are we not jumping out of this plane?
我们不从这架飞机上跳下去吗？
- I thought you said you were scared.
- 我以为你说你害怕。
- I was, until you got here.
- 我是害怕，直到你来了。
- What about Ricky?
- 那Ricky呢？
- I flew.
- 我飞了。
That was the most exhilarating experience of my life!
那是我一生中最令人兴奋的经历！
Let's all jump, together.
我们一起跳吧。
- Let's... both: Do it!
- 我们... 一起：跳吧！
- Whoo! - Okay.
哇！好的。
- All right, "I love you guys" on three.
好吧，三个人一起说‘我爱你们’。
Ready?
准备好了吗？
One, two, three!
一，二，三！
all: I love you guys!
我们都爱你们！
- All right, step number one:
好的，第一步：
never jump past the drop zone.
永远不要跳过降落区。
Whoops.
哎呀。
♪ ♪
- ♪ There's four holes in my roof ♪ - [plays blues riffs]
♪ 我的屋顶有四个洞 ♪
- ♪ And there's one thing I know ♪
♪ 我知道一件事 ♪
♪ This is gonna cost us ♪
♪ 这会让我们花费 ♪
♪ A whole lot of dough ♪
♪ 一大笔钱 ♪
- Even though that was completely insane,
尽管那完全疯狂，
it was one of the best moments of my life.
那是我一生中最棒的时刻之一。
- Of our lives.
是我们一生中最棒的时刻之一。
- Well, at least nothing is ever boring
至少，在哈珀家永远不会无聊。
in the Harper house. - [chuckles]
（轻笑）
- And nothing ever will be.
而且永远都不会无聊。
[laughter]
（笑声）
[dog barking]
狗叫声
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
[whistling]
口哨声
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪